Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Photographs-Topical, 1955-1995; 5 linear feet
  - Michigan Land Trust Fund (Box 38)
  - Michigan Student Assembly, 1986-1993 (Box 38)
  - Museums (including Ann Arbor), 1954-1993 (Box 38)
  - Performance, 5 folders
    - Dance, 1985-1993 (Box 38)
    - Music, 2 folders
      - Local and impromptu, 1984-1993; undated (Box 38)
      - Professional/famous, 1982-1993 (Box 38)
    - Theater, 1987-1993; undated (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box 38)
  - Personalities (famous people, e.g. Jimmy Hoffa, Arthur Miller), 1988-1993; undated (Box 38)
    (See also-Speakers)
  - Phoenix Laboratory (Box 38)
    (See-Campus Locations-North Campus)
  - Plant and grounds, 1958-1993 (Box 38)
  - Police and law enforcement, 1971-1993 (Box 39)
  - Politics, government, etc., 5 folders
    - Local, 1922-1993 (Box 39)
    - National/Presidential, 1960-1993 (Box 39)
    - State, 1988-1993; undated (Box 39)
    - United States Congress, 1984-1993; undated (Box 39)
    - Voting on campus, 1971-1993 (Box 39)
  - Pow Wow (Box 39)
    (See-Ann Arbor area-Festivals)
  - Puerto Rico, 1959 (Box 39)
  - Recycling and waste management, 1987-1992; undated (Box 39)
  - Regents, 1978-1992; undated (Box 39)
  - Research (including non-University of Michigan), 1981-1993; undated (Box 39)
  - Seasons and holidays, 1959-1993 (Box 39)
  - Speakers, 1982-1993; undated (Box 39)
    (See also-Politics, government, etc.)
  - Student life, 10 folders
    (See also-Dormitories, Classes)
    - Bodies (Piercing, tattoos, etc.), 1991-1992 (Box 39)
    - Campus organizations and activities (ROTC, Glee Club, religious organizations, etc.), 1959-1993 (Box 39)
    - Diag, 1985-1993 (Box 39)
    - Employment, 1992-1993 (Box 39)
    - Individual students, 1985-1993 (Box 39)
    - Sports, recreation, and exercise, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Spring Break, 1985-1986 (Box 39)
    - Studying, 1985-1993 (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1993; undated (Box 39)
  - Union, Michigan Union activities, 1988-1993 (Box 39)
  - University of Michigan
    - Offices, 1990-1993; undated (Box 39)
    - Schools and Departments
      (See also-Classes and Teaching Assistants)
      - Architecture and Design, 1970s-1992 (Box 39)
      - Art, 1972-1993 (Box 39)
      - Astronomy, 1958-1993 (Box 39)
      - Dance (Box 39)
        (See "Performance-Dance.")
      - Engineering, 1959-1993 (Box 39)
      - Law, 1956-1993 (Box 39)
      - Medicine, Dentistry, and Nursing, 1958-1993 (Box 39)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1971 (Box 39)
        (includes Education, Forestry, and Geology)
      - Music, 1960-1993 (Box 39)
      - Pharmacy, 1958; undated (Box 39)
  - Vendors and vending (including Farmers Market), 1986-1993 (Box 39)
- Digital Media-Chronological, 1993-2006
  The Digital Media series consists of 1 linear foot of digital images on various storage formats, including DVD-RAM disks, DVD-R discs, magneto-optical disks, and CDs. When possible, images have been migrated from obsolete formats onto 4.7 GB DVD-R discs. the material was received in a 2006 accession transferred by Sam Offen on behalf of Tony Ding who served as photo editor of The Michigan Daily from 2003-2005.
  - 1993
    - October 1993-December 1995
    - Copy of Photo Archive, 1993-1994
    - Complete Archive, 1993-1995; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
  - 1994
    - 1994
  - 1995
    - Copy of Photo Archive, Part 1, 1995
    - Photo Archive, Part 2, 1995
    - Photo Archive, Part C, 1995
    - Photo Archive, v. 2 and 3, 1995; 1 magneto-optical discs (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
    - Photo Archive, v. 4, 1995; 1 magneto-optical discs (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
    - Photo Archive, #1, 1995; 1 magneto-optical discs (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
    - Photo Archive, #2, 1995; 1 magneto-optical discs (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
    - Photo Archive, #3, 1995; 1 magneto-optical discs (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
    - Miscellanneous, 1995
  - 1996
    - Michigan Daily, #1, 1996
    - Photo Archive, Part 1, 1996
    - Copy of Photo Archive, #3, 1996
    - Photo Archive, #4, 1996
  - 1997
    - January-October 1997
    - January-February 1997
    - Photo Archive, October 1997-March 1998
    - Photo Archive, Part 3, 1997
    - January-October 1997, September-December 1997; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
    - December 1997-March 1998, March - August 1998; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
  - 1998
    - March 1998-December 1998
    - October 1998-March 1999, March-October 1999; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
  - 1999
    - January 1999-October 1999
    - August 1999-December 1999
    - August-December 1999, January-September 2000; 1 DVD-RAMs
    - Photo Archive, 1999-2000
  - 2000
    - April-September 2000
    - October-December 2000
  - 2001
    - 2001
    - October 2001
    - November 2001
    - Sports Archive, 2001-2003
    - Photo Archive, 2001; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
  - 2002
    - 2002
    - Photo Archive, January-August 2002; September-December 2002; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
  - 2003
    - Sports Archive, 2001-2003
    - Photo Archive, 2003
  - 2004
    - Photo Archive and Photo Archive Specials, v. 1, October-December 2000; 2004; 1 DVD-RAMs (Box 40)
    - Michigan Daily Photo Archive, January-June 2004
    - Michigan Daily Photo Archive, July-November 2004
  - 2006
    - October-December 2006
  - Undated
    - Michigan Daily Photo, 1 removable hard disks (5.25 in.) (Box 40)
- Negatives By Photographer, 1980-2004
  The Michigan Daily negatives received in the 2006 accession consist of 5 linear feet of primarily 35 millimeter negatives taken by Michigan Daily photographers between the years of 1980 and 2004 and are divided into three series: Photographers (arranged alphabetically by last name of photographer with dates when possible. Many of the negatives were indexed according to the photographers' initials, and full names have been provided when possible.), Topical (arranged alphabetically by subject with dates when possible), and Chronological (arranged by year, from 1993 to 2002). The fourth series, Guidelines, consists of two folders of textual documents relating to the creation and submission of Michigan Daily photographic materials.
  - Baker, ?, undated (Box 41)
  - Bradley-Swift, Jen, 1996-1997; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Braun, Lauren, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Camp, Chris, 1999 (Box 41)
  - Collins, Sarah, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Cook, Diane, 1996 (Box 41)
  - Deth, Josh, 1992 (Box 41)
  - Feldkamp, Tom, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Fosdick, Emma, 2001; 2002 (Box 41)
  - Freeman, Rick, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Friedman, Mark, 1993-1997 (Box 41)
  - Gilmore, Rob, 1997 (Box 41)
  - G, Yoni [Goldstein, Yehonatan], 2001 (Box 41)
  - Handleman, Karen, undated (Box 41)
  - Hurand, Shoshana, 2002 (Box 41)
  - Isaak, Susan, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Jacobs, Joy, 1997; 1998 (Box 41)
  - Kalick, Danny, 1999-2000; 3 folders (Box 41)
  - Kleinbaum, Josh, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Krauss, ?, 1992 (Box 41)
  - Linn, Emily, 1999 (Box 41)
  - Lipinski, Scott, undated (Box 41)
  - M[izel], Debra, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Madill, Matt, undated (Box 42)
  - Matthews, Peter, 1992 (Box 42)
  - McLellan, Bryan, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Menchik, Jeremy, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Daily Scholarship Photographs, April 10, 2000
  - Moloshok, Danny, undated; 6 slides (color) (Box 42)
  - Myers, Margaret, 1996 (Box 42)
  - Nathan, Emily, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Oh, Miyon, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Petrie, ?, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Pratt, John, 2001 (Box 42)
  - Ruffer, Frederick, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Sachs, Karen, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Schaefer, Kristin, 1995-1997; 3 folders (Box 42)
  - [Schreiber], Andi, 1998 (Box 42)
  - Stevens, Molly, 1992; 1994 (Box 42)
  - Stillman, Sara, 1998 (Box 42)
  - Sumner, Jonathan, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Talanian, Paul, 1998; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Tomlin, ?., 2001 (Box 43)
  - Triest, Jonathan, 2001 (Box 43)
  - Van Dyke, Walker, 1995-1996; 4 folders (Box 43)
  - Ward, Leslie, 2001 (Box 43)
  - Westrate, Joseph, 1995; 3 folders (Box 43)
  - White, Ellie, 2001; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Wolk, Alex, 2000 (Box 43)
  - Yogachi, Kimitsu, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Young, Andy, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Unidentified
    - A.J.A, 1996-1997 (Box 43)
    - L.A.B, 2001-2002 (Box 43)
    - Dean (Box 43)
    - D.O.D, 1999 (Box 43)
    - G.E., 1999 (Box 43)
    - J.M.F., 2000 (Box 43)
    - Gabe, 1999 (Box 43)
    - K.A.R., 2000 (Box 43)
    - K.K.T., 2001 (Box 43)
- Negatives-Chronological, 1993-2002
  - 1993 (Box 44)
  - 1994 (Box 44)
  - 1995 (Box 44)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 44)
  - 1998 (Box 44)
  - 1999 (Box 44)
  - 2000 (Box 44)
  - 2001-2002 (Box 44)
- Negatives-Topical, 1993-2002
  - Buildings, 1994-1997 (Box 44)
  - Detroit Project, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
  - Events
    - Events, 1993; 1997 (Box 44)
    - Concerts (Box 44)
      (named; includes XTC; Jeff Beck; Todd Rundgren; Phish)
    - Performances, 1993-2001 (Box 44)
    - Protests/Demonstrations, 1993-2002 (Box 44)
      (includes prints)
    - Speakers/Conferences, 1993-2001 (Box 44)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1994-1998 (Box 44)
  - Michigan Daily
    - Fashion, 1996 undated (Box 44)
    - Features, 1993-1997; undated (Box 44)
    - Headshots, 1993-2001 (Box 44)
  - MSA, 1995-2001 (Box 44)
  - Notable People, 1994-2000 (Box 44)
    (includes Bill Clinton; Mike Wallace; Wynton Marsalis; John Engler, John McCain; Michael Moore; Lee Bollinger; Jesse Jackson; Joe Fitzsimmons; Ronna Romney)
  - Sports
    - Baseball, 1995-1998 (Box 44)
    - Basketball (Men's), 1993-1994; 2 folders
      - NCAA tournament, 1994; 1 box (Box 44)
    - Basketball (Women's), 1996-2000 (Box 44)
    - Biking, 1995 undated (Box 44)
    - Crew, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Football
      - Football, 1993-1994 (Box 44)
      - "MEG Football '92-'93", 1 film reels (Box 44)
    - Gymnastics, 1994-1997; undated (Box 45)
    - Hockey, 1993-2000; undated; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Lacrosse, 1996; 2001 (Box 45)
    - Rugby (Women's), undated (Box 45)
    - Soccer (Men's and Women's), 1993-2000 (Box 45)
    - Softball, 1995-1997; undated (Box 45)
    - Swimming, 1996 undated (Box 45)
    - Tennis (Men's and Women's), 1996-2001; undated (Box 45)
    - Track, 1994-2001 (Box 45)
    - Volleyball, 1993-1997 (Box 45)
    - Wrestling, 1996-2001; undated (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 45)
  - United Auto Workers Strike, 1998 (Box 45)
  - Unidentified, 4 folders (Box 45)
- Guidelines
  - Photo Guidelines (Box 45)
  - Michigan Daily Photo Department Handbook, 1997 (Box 45)
A nearly complete run of The Michigan Daily student newspaper is available online in the Michigan Daily Digital Archive.